<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>s3 on</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/tags/s3/</link><description>Recent content in s3 on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wiki.connerv.com/tags/s3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Athena</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/athena/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/athena/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki S3 S3 Select Athena Amazon Athena is an interactive query service that makes it easy to analyze data in Amazon S3 using standard SQL expressions.</description></item><item><title>Macie</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/macie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/macie/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki S3 Macie is an ML-powered security service that helps you prevent data loss by automatically discovering, classifying, and protecting sensitive data stored in Amazon S3.</description></item><item><title>S3</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki S3 Access Logs S3 Access Points S3 Cors S3 Encryption S3 Events S3 Inventory S3 Lifecycle Configuration S3 Object Lock S3 Object Storage Class S3 Object Versioning and MFA Delete S3 Presigned URLs S3 Replication S3 Select S3 Security S3 Static Website Hosting Simple Storage Service (S3) Amazon S3 now provides increased performance to support at least 3,500 requests per second to add data and 5,500 requests per second to retrieve data, which can save significant processing time for no additional charge.</description></item><item><title>S3 Access Points</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-access-points/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-access-points/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Access Points Simply managing access at scale for applications using shared data sets on S3 buckets.</description></item><item><title>S3 CORS</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-cors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-cors/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 CORS Same-origin requests are always allowed, defined on initial request. Example is an S3 bucket that loads an index.</description></item><item><title>S3 Encryption</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-encryption/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-encryption/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Encryption Buckets aren&amp;rsquo;t encrypted, encryption is defined at the object level 2 methods of encryption that S3 supports, both are encryption at rest.</description></item><item><title>S3 Events</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-events/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Events A feature that allows you to create event notification configurations on a bucket Supports SNS, SQS, Lambda functions, etc.</description></item><item><title>S3 Inventory</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-inventory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-inventory/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Inventory Amazon S3 Inventory is one of the tools Amazon S3 provides to help manage your storage.</description></item><item><title>S3 Lifecycle Configuration</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-lifecycle-configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-lifecycle-configuration/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Object Storage Class S3 Lifecycle Configuration A set of rules, consisting of actions Rules can apply to an entire bucket, or groups of objects Transition Actions move objects to a different Object Storage Class Transitions can only happen in a downward direction Be aware of the 30 day S3 waiting period before you can transition an object Expiration Actions can delete Objects or Object Versions after a certain time period</description></item><item><title>S3 Object Lock</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-object-lock/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-object-lock/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Object Lock Object Lock enables a Write-Once-Read-Many (WORM) - No Delete, No Overwrite</description></item><item><title>S3 Object Storage Class</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-object-storage-class/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-object-storage-class/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Object Storage Classes S3 Standard Objects are replicated across at least 3 AZs in the AWS region Data is available within milliseconds Billed GB/m fee for data stored Billed $ per GB for transfer OUT (IN is free) and a price per 1,000 requests No specific retrieval fee No minimum duration No minimum size S3 Standard-IA (Infrequent Access) Same specs as S3 Standard, but object storage costs are significantly cheaper New cost component, which is a retrieval fee, in the form of a per GB data retrieval fee.</description></item><item><title>S3 Object Versioning and MFA Delete</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-object-versioning-and-mfa-delete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-object-versioning-and-mfa-delete/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Object Versioning Controlled at the bucket level This is disabled by default, but once it is enabled, it CANNOT be disabled, but it can be suspended (which is effectively the same thing) You will continue to be billed for all Object versions, even when Object Versioning is suspended Without Object Versioning being enabled, each object is solely identified by it&amp;rsquo;s key, which is unique inside the bucket If you modify an object, the previous version is deleted Object Versioning allows you to store multiple versions of an object within a bucket When an object with KEY = cat.</description></item><item><title>S3 PreSigned URLs</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-presigned-urls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-presigned-urls/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Presigned URLs Give another person or application access to an object inside of an S3 bucket, using your credentials in a safe and secure way Either you or an automated process can generated a presigned URL, which has specific access permissions encoded within it.</description></item><item><title>S3 Replication</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-replication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-replication/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Replication S3 has replication features which allow objects to be replicated between a SOURCE and DESTINATION bucket in the same or different AWS accounts.</description></item><item><title>S3 Security</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-security/</guid><description>Related Notes s3 Useful Links Bucket Policy Examples S3 Security S3 is private by default.</description></item><item><title>S3 Select</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-select/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-select/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki S3 Athena S3 Select Amazon S3 Select is designed to help analyze and process data within an object in Amazon S3 buckets, faster and cheaper.</description></item><item><title>S3 Static Website Hosting</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-static-website-hosting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-static-website-hosting/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Static Website Hosting Normally, you&amp;rsquo;d use AWS S3 APIs to access S3 However, when S3 Static Website Hosting is enabled, you can access S3 via standard HTTP This allows you to host almost anything When enabling, you must set an Index (default page) and Error (default, when something goes wrong) HTML document When enabled, a Website Endpoint is created.</description></item></channel></rss>