<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cvwiki on</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/</link><description>Recent content in cvwiki on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wiki.connerv.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/amazon-inspector/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/amazon-inspector/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Amazon Inspector Scans EC2 instance &amp;amp; the instance OS Also containers Detects vulnerabilities and deviations against best practice Length: 15 minutes, 1 hour, 8/12 hours or 1 day Provides a report of findings ordered by priority Network Assessment (no agent required) Network &amp;amp; Host Assessment (requires agent) Host Assessment Rules Packages (Important for exam): Common vulnerabilities and exposures (CVE) List of CVE ids that are generated as part of a report for an instance or container Center for Internet Security (CIS) Benchmarks Best practices from CIS test against instance or container Security best practices for Amazon Inspector Network Reachability (no agent required) Check readability end to end of EC2, ALB, DX, ELB, ENI, IGW, ACLs, RT&amp;rsquo;s, SG&amp;rsquo;s, Subnets, VPCs, VGWs &amp;amp; VPC Peering Network Reachability Rules Packages (Important for exam): RecognizedPortWithListener RecognizedPortNoListener RecognizedPortNoAgent UnrecognizedPortWithListener With Inspector, rules packages determine what is checked Agent can provide additional OS visibility, such as Amazon Inspector is a vulnerability management service that continuously scans your AWS Workloads for vulnerabilities.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-appsync/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-appsync/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AppSync AWS AppSync is a fully managed service that makes it easy to develop GraphQL APIs by handling the heavy lifting of securely connecting to data sources like AWS DynamoDB, Lambda, and more.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/elastic-beanstalk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/elastic-beanstalk/</guid><description>Parent Wiki: [[aws-wiki]]
Elastic Beanstalk’s main benefits include timesaving server configuration, powerful customization, and a cost-effective price point.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/rds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/rds/</guid><description>Related Notes [[aws-wiki]] [[aurora]] Useful Links RDS Pricing RDS Free Tier How to connect To RDS with MySQL Client: This simplified guide was pulled from this AWS Docs page: Connecting to a DB instance running the MySQL database engine.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-access-logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-access-logs/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Access Logs Typically, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a Source Bucket and a Target Bucket You must enable access logging inside of the Source Bucket to use this feature Log Delivery Group needs write access to the Target Bucket Log files are delivered in new line delimited files that contain records.</description></item><item><title>Air Fried Broccoli</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/air-fried-frozen-broccoli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/air-fried-frozen-broccoli/</guid><description>Ingredients 24 oz frozen broccoli florets 1/2 teaspoon salt 1/2 teaspoon pepper 1 teaspoon garlic powder 3/4 teaspoon onion powder olive oil spray Cooking Equipment Air Fryer Instructions Make sure the air fryer is clean.</description></item><item><title>Amazon GuardDuty</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/amazon-guardduty/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/amazon-guardduty/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Amazon GuardDuty Continuous security monitoring service Analyzes supported Data Sources Uses AI/ML, plus threat intelligence feeds Identifies unexpected and unauthorized activity Attempts to learn your normal activity on its own, and spot activity outside of normal patterns Notify or event-driven protection/remediation Supports multiple accounts (MASTER and MEMBER)</description></item><item><title>API Gateway</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/api-gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/api-gateway/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki API Gateway WebSockets As a heads up as well to anyone doing IoT-related things.</description></item><item><title>Athena</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/athena/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/athena/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki S3 S3 Select Athena Amazon Athena is an interactive query service that makes it easy to analyze data in Amazon S3 using standard SQL expressions.</description></item><item><title>Aurora</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aurora/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aurora/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Relational Database Service Aurora Key Differences Compared to RDS Aurora is hosted within RDS, but it has a different enough architecture that it deserves a dedicated page.</description></item><item><title>Awesome GitHub Projects</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/awesome-git-repositories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/awesome-git-repositories/</guid><description> GitHub Greatest hits list of archived repositories on GitHub: Nintendo Switch Emulator</description></item><item><title>AWS App Runner</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-app-runner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-app-runner/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Useful Links AWS App Runner Pricing AWS App Runner</description></item><item><title>AWS Artifact</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-artifact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-artifact/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Artifact AWS Artifact is your go-to, central resource for compliance-related information that matters to you.</description></item><item><title>AWS Backup</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-backup/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Relational Database Service EFS Backup AWS Backup enables you to centralize and automate data protection across AWS services and hybrid workloads.</description></item><item><title>AWS Batch</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-batch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-batch/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Batch AWS Batch is aimed at the specific use case of executing batch jobs that are pulled from a queue.</description></item><item><title>AWS Certificate Manager</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-certificate-manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-certificate-manager/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Certificate Manager AWS Certificate Manager (ACM) lets you import 3rd party certificates from the ACM console, as well as programmatically.</description></item><item><title>AWS Cloud Map</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloud-map/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloud-map/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Cloud Map AWS Cloud Map is a cloud resource discovery service. With Cloud Map, you can define custom names for your application resources, and it maintains the updated location of these dynamically changing resources.</description></item><item><title>AWS Config</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-config/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Config Primary function is to record configuration changes over time (configuration items) on resources, and grouping this information into configuration histories</description></item><item><title>AWS Control Tower</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-control-tower/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-control-tower/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Control Tower Allows quick and easy setup of multi-account environment Orchestrates other AWS services to provide this functionality Leverages Organizations, IAM Identity Center (formerly AWS SSO), CloudFormation, AWS Config and AWS Service Catalog Landing Zone - multi-account environment SSO/ID Federation, Centralized Logging and Auditing Guard Rails - Detect/Mandate rules/standards across all accounts Config is used under the hood to implement these guardrails Account Factory - Automates and Standardizes new account creation Basic template is applied (CloudFormation is used under the hood for this) Dashboard - single page oversight of the entire environment Landing Zone Allows for implementation of a Well Architected multi-account environment Home Region - The region you initially deploy into You can explicitly allow or deny the usage of other regions Built with Organizations, Config and CloudFormation Security OU - Log Archive &amp;amp; Audit Accounts (CloudTrail &amp;amp; Config Logs) Sandbox OU - Test/less rigid security You can create other OU&amp;rsquo;s and Accounts IAM Identity Center (AWS SSO) - SSO, multiple accounts, ID Federation (use existing identity stores) Monitoring and Notifications - CloudWatch and SNS End User account provisioning using Service Catalog Guard Rails Guardrails are rules - multi-account governance Mandatory, Strongly Recommended or Elective Preventative - Stop you from doing things (AWS ORG SCP) enforced or not enabled i.</description></item><item><title>AWS Cost Explorer</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-cost-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-cost-explorer/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Cost Explorer Capable of analyzing usage within the account, and giving recommendations about reserved instance purchases (if you have enough usage on the account) Cost Anomaly Detection: Help reduces cost with machine learning by tracking costs and usage Rightsizing Recommendations: Reviews historical EC2 usage to identify opportunities for greater cost and usage efficiency Cost Allocation Tags Cost allocation tags - have to be enabled individually (per account for standard accounts or ORG Master for ORGS) AWS Generated - e.</description></item><item><title>AWS Directory Service</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-directory-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-directory-service/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Directory Service AWS Directory Service for Microsoft Active Directory, also known as AWS Managed Microsoft Active Directory (AD), enables your directory-aware workloads and AWS resources to use managed Active Directory (AD) in AWS.</description></item><item><title>AWS Firewall Manager</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-firewall-manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-firewall-manager/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki [[aws-web-application-firewall]] #aws-sysops #aws-security</description></item><item><title>AWS Glue</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-glue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-glue/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Glue AWS Glue is a serverless, fully managed extract, transform, and load (ETL) service that makes it easy for customers to prepare and load their data for analytics.</description></item><item><title>AWS KMS</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-kms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-kms/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki CloudHSM Key Management Service (KMS) Regional and Public Service Every region is isolated when using KMS Create, Store and Manage Cryptographic Keys Allows creation of both symmetric and asymmetric keys Allows you to perform cryptographic operations (encryption, decryption, etc.</description></item><item><title>AWS Lambda</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/lambda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/lambda/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Lambda AWS Lambda lets you run code without provisioning or managing servers. You pay only for the compute time you consume.</description></item><item><title>AWS Organizations</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/organizations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/organizations/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Organizations AWS Organizations is an account management services that lets you consolidate multiple AWS accounts into an organization that you create and centrally manage.</description></item><item><title>AWS Service Catalog</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-service-catalog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-service-catalog/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Service Catalog AWS Service Catalog enables a (usually internal user) to directly users or customers to deploy infrastructure with tight control in a self-service way</description></item><item><title>AWS Shield</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-shield/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-shield/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Web Application Firewall AWS Shield Types of Attack Network Volumetric Attacks (L3) - Saturate Capacity These types of attacks overwhelm a system by directing as much raw network data at a target as possible Network Protocol Attacks (L4) - TCP SYN Flood Flood large number of connections, leave connections open, preventing new ones Analogy is people calling a call center, and staying on the phone lines, preventing real customers from talking to call center employees L4 can also have a volumetric component Application Layer Attacks (L7) - e.</description></item><item><title>AWS Site-to-Site VPN</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/site-to-site-vpn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/site-to-site-vpn/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Direct Connect AWS Site-to-Site VPN Offers the quickest way to create a network link between an AWS environment and an on-premises environment, or another cloud.</description></item><item><title>AWS Snowball</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-snowball/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-snowball/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Snowball AWS Snowball is a petabyte-scale data transport solution that uses secure appliances to transfer large amounts of data into and out of the AWS cloud.</description></item><item><title>AWS Step Functions</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-step-functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-step-functions/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Lambda AWS SWF Helpful Links AWS Step Functions Pricing Step Functions AWS Step Functions provides serverless orchestration for modern applications.</description></item><item><title>AWS SWF</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-swf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-swf/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Step Functions AWS Simple Workflow Service (SWF) Consider using AWS Step Functions for all your new applications, since it provides a more productive and agile approach to coordinating application components using visual workflows.</description></item><item><title>AWS VPC</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpc/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Virtual Private Cloud (AWS VPC) Note: /32 after an IP address denotes one IP address, while /0 refers to the entire network.</description></item><item><title>AWS Web Application Firewall</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-web-application-firewall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-web-application-firewall/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Firewall Manager Web Application Firewall (WAF) AWS Implementation of Layer 7 firewall (HTTP/HTTPS) The WAF Web ACL can be associated with Global resources like CloudFront, and regional resources, like ALB, API Gateway, etc.</description></item><item><title>AWS Wiki</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-wiki/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-wiki/</guid><description>AWS Wiki Helpful Links AWS Pricing Calculator AWS Documentation AWS Extend Switch Roles AWS Services AWS Artifact API Gateway AWS AppSync Athena Aurora AWS Backup AWS Batch AWS Cost Explorer AWS Certificate Manager Cloud Map CloudFront CloudHSM CloudEndure Data Lifecycle Manager DataSync AWS Directory Service EBS Elasticsearch EFS EKS Elastic Beanstalk Elastic Map Reduce FSx for Windows File Server FSx for Lustre AWS Glue IoT core Kinesis MQ Amazon Neptune Redshift Resource Access Manager Route 53 AWS Service Catalog AWS Shield AWS SWF Simple Queue Service AWS Snowball Simple Notification Service Storage Gateway WorkDocs AWS WorkSpaces Compute Lambda EC2 ECS Fargate Serverless Workflows AWS Step Functions S3 S3 S3 Select Macie - ML-based Data Classification in S3 Resource Provisioning and Deployment Automation CloudFormation CodeBuild CodePipeline CodeDeploy CDK Systems Manager OpsWorks Cache Elasticache Database DynamoDB DynamoDB Accelerator RDS Monitoring CloudWatch AWS Config CloudTrail AWS X-Ray User Management &amp;amp; Security IAM Organizations IAM Identity Center Cognito AWS Control Tower Security Amazon GuardDuty AWS Firewall Manager AWS Web Application Firewall AWS KMS Networking Direct Connect VPC NACLs and Security Groups VPC Router VPC Peering Internet Gateway VPC Gateway Endpoints VPC Interface Endpoints Egress Only Internet Gateway NAT Gateway VPN CloudHub Transit Gateway PrivateLink Site-to-Site VPN Global Accelerator Miscellaneous Public vs Private vs Multi vs Hybrid Cloud Public Cloud = using 1 public cloud Private Cloud = using on-premises real cloud Multi-Cloud = using more than 1 public cloud Hybrid Cloud = Public and Private Clouds Hybrid Cloud is NOT public cloud + legacy on-premises Security Best Practices Q: An application is hosted in an Auto Scaling group of EC2 instances and a Microsoft SQL Server on Amazon RDS.</description></item><item><title>AWS WorkSpaces</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-workspaces/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-workspaces/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki WorkSpaces Amazon WorkSpaces is a fully managed desktop virtualization service for Windows and Linux that enables you to access resources from any supported device.</description></item><item><title>AWS X-Ray</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-x-ray/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-x-ray/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki X Ray Distributed tracing application
Tracing Header - first service generates .</description></item><item><title>Bash</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/bash/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/bash/</guid><description>Helpful Links Bash Hacker&amp;rsquo;s Wiki Wooledge&amp;rsquo;s Wiki Shell Script Best Practices, from a decade of scripting things Infinite Loop Because sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s just necessary to have an infinite loop.</description></item><item><title>Blueberry Oatmeal</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/blueberry-oatmeal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/blueberry-oatmeal/</guid><description>Steps Make oatmeal on stove or in microwave. Throw Trader Joe&amp;rsquo;s organic frozen blueberries in halfway through. Mix in desired amount of chia seeds and serve.</description></item><item><title>Bone Broth Rice</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/bone-broth-rice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/bone-broth-rice/</guid><description>Ingredients Use 1:2 ratio cups of rice to cups of bone broth. For example, 1 cup of rice and 2 cups of bone broth.</description></item><item><title>CloudFormation</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloudformation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloudformation/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Resources CloudFormation Docs CloudFormation User Guide CloudFormation Template Reference CloudFormation CloudFormation begins with a template, which is a document written in JSON or YAML.</description></item><item><title>CloudFront</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloudfront/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloudfront/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki CloudFront CloudFront is a Content Delivery network (CDN) within AWS Improves the delivery of content by caching and using an efficient global network When a user makes a request, the following happens in the CloudFront Network: Checks closest Edge Location.</description></item><item><title>CloudHSM</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloudhsm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloudhsm/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki CloudHSM A cloud based hardware security modules (HSM) that enables you to easily generate and use your own encryption keys on the AWS Cloud.</description></item><item><title>CloudTrail</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloudtrail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloudtrail/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki CloudTrail Almost everything that can be done to an AWS account is logged by CloudTrail Logs API calls/account activities as a CloudTrail Event Actions taken by users, roles or services 90 days stored by default in Event History, S3 CloudTrail logs storage are not included by default Enabled by default - no cost for 90 day history To customize the service, create 1 or more Trails CloudTrail Logs are encrypted by default with Amazon S3 server-side encryption CloudTrail is a service that enables governance, compliance, operational auditing, and risk auditing of your AWS account.</description></item><item><title>CloudWatch</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloudwatch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloudwatch/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki CloudWatch Ingest, store and manage metrics
Public Service - public space endpoints (can be accessed both on-prem or on AWS) Needs public internet access to access the public space endpoint AWS Service integration - management place Agent integration .</description></item><item><title>CodeBuild</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/codebuild/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/codebuild/</guid><description>Related Notes [AWS Wiki] CodeBuild You can run CodeBuild locally to test out BuildSpecs without needing to put them onto the Cloud every time</description></item><item><title>Creamy Tortellini Spinach Chicken Soup</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/creamy-tortellini-spinach-chicken-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/creamy-tortellini-spinach-chicken-soup/</guid><description>Cooking equipment Instant Pot 1 tbsp measure 1/2 tsp measure 1 cup measure 1/2 cup measure Ingredients 1 tbsp of Olive oil 1 yellow onion, diced 3 tsp garlic minced 4 cups chicken broth 1 to 1 1/2 lbs boneless, skinless chicken thighs 1 Tbsp dried basil 2 Tbsp tomato paste 2 (14.</description></item><item><title>Curl</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/curl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/curl/</guid><description>curl resources Curl Man Page Curl Command Cheat Sheet useful curl commands Pipe curl command output to json_pp to pretty print json response 1 $CURL_COMMAND | json_pp Curl Timeouts curl --max-time &amp;lt;seconds&amp;gt; or curl -m &amp;lt;seconds&amp;gt; There is no difference between -v, -vv, and -vvv in curl Explanation via Stack Overflow 1 curl -vvv -sSL -o /dev/null &amp;#39;https://google.</description></item><item><title>Data Lifecycle Manager</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/data-lifecycle-manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/data-lifecycle-manager/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki DLM - Data Lifecycle Manager (EBS Volume Snapshot Management) You can use Amazon Data Lifecycle Manager (Amazon DLM) to automate the creation, retention, and deletion of snapshots taken to back up your Amazon EBS volumes.</description></item><item><title>DataSync</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/datasync/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/datasync/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS DataSync (moves/migrates data) Fastest on-prem storage to cloud storage data migration service, used more for historical archival or long term storage AWS DataSync allows you to copy large datasets with millions of files, without having to build custom solutions with open source tools, or license and manage expensive commercial network acceleration software.</description></item><item><title>Direct Connect (DX)</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/direct-connect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/direct-connect/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Site-to-Site VPN Transit Gateway Direct Connect Direct Connect is AWS&amp;rsquo;s physical private link connecting your business premises to its public and private services</description></item><item><title>Disaster Recovery Scenarios</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/disaster-recover-scenarios/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/disaster-recover-scenarios/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Disaster Recovery Scenarios (Route 53, CloudWatch) Use an active-passive failover configuration when you want a primary resource or group of resources to be available majority of the time and you want a secondary resource or group of resources to be on standby in case all the primary resources become unavailable.</description></item><item><title>Docker</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/Docker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/Docker/</guid><description>Writing a Dockerfile for Spring Use docker multi stage build 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 FROMmaven:3.</description></item><item><title>DynamoDB</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/dynamodb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/dynamodb/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki DAX - DynamoDB Accelerator DynamoDB The partition key portion of a table&amp;rsquo;s primary key determines the logical partitions in which a table&amp;rsquo;s data is stored.</description></item><item><title>DynamoDB Accelerator</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/dynamodb-accelerator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/dynamodb-accelerator/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki DynamoDB DAX - DynamoDB Accelerator DAX is a fully managed, highly available, in-memory cache for Amazon DynamoDB that delivers up to a 10 times performance improvement - from milliseconds to microseconds - even at millions of requests per second.</description></item><item><title>EBS</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ebs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ebs/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki EBS - Elastic Block Store EBS provides block level storage volumes for use with EC2 instances.</description></item><item><title>EC2</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki EC2 Purchase Options EC2 Placement Groups EC2 - Elastic Compute Cloud Instance Types Instance Types C: Compute Optimized Instances Cost-effective high performance at a low price per compute ratio Note that c1 type instance do not support IPv6 D: Storage Optimized Instances High disk throughput G: Accelerated Computing Instances Graphics-intensive GPU instances H: Storage Optimized Instances HDD-based local storage for high disk throughput I: Storage Optimized Instances High storage instances, low latency, high random I/O performance, high sequential read throughput, and high IOPS M: General Purpose Instances Fixed performance Note that m3 type instance do not support IPv6 P: Accelerated Computing Instances General purpose GPU instances F: Accelerated Computing Instances Reconfigurable FPGA instances R: Memory Optimized Instances Memory-intensive applications T: General Purpose Instances Burstable performance instances X: Memory Optimized Instances Large-scale, enterprise-class, in-memory applications, and high-performance databases EC2 Storage Some EC2 instance types come with a form of directly attached, block-storage known as the instance store.</description></item><item><title>EC2 Placement Groups</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2-placement-groups/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2-placement-groups/</guid><description>Related Notes EC2 EC2 Placement Group Allows you to influence physical placement of EC2 instances within AWS Cluster Placement Groups (Performance) Generally, instances in this placement group will use the same rack, and sometime even the same host.</description></item><item><title>EC2 Purchase Options</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2-purchase-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2-purchase-options/</guid><description>Related Notes EC2 EC2 Purchase Options (Launch Types) On Demand Default purchase option Isolated instances, but multiple customer instances run on the same shared hardware Instances of different sizes run on the same EC2 hosts - consuming a defined allocation of resources Uses per-second billing while an instance is running.</description></item><item><title>ECS</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ecs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ecs/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Fargate #ecs- Elastic Container Service Avoid ECS Downtime StackOverflow: Restart ECS service with no downtime To avoid downtime, you should manipulate 2 parameters: minimum healthy percent and maximum percent: For example, if your service has a desired number of four tasks and a maximum percent value of 200%, the scheduler may start four new tasks before stopping the four older tasks (provided that the cluster resources required to do this are available).</description></item><item><title>EFS - Elastic File System</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/efs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/efs/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki EC2 EFS - Elastic File System Moves EC2 to be closer to being stateless Implementation of NFSv4 EFS Filesystems can be mounted in Linux only Uses POSIX permissions, a standard understood by all linux systems Shared between many EC2 Instances Private service, via mount targets inside a VPC Mount targets must be present in each AZ that a VPC uses to provide high availability Mount targets are what the EC2 instances use to connect to the EFS Can be accessed from on-premises via VPN or DX General Purpose and Max I/O performance mode Max I/O is good for highly parallel services Bursting and Provisioned Throughput Modes Storage Classes Standard (default) Infrequent Access (lower cost) Lifecycle Policies can be used with classes Amazon EFS is a fully-managed service that makes it easy to set up and scale file storage in the Amazon Cloud.</description></item><item><title>Egress-Only Internet Gateway</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/egress-only-internet-gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/egress-only-internet-gateway/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki NAT Gateway Egress-Only Internet Gateway Egress-Only Internet Gateway is an outbound-only Internet Gateway that allows private IPv6 resources in your VPC&amp;rsquo;s private subnets to initiate a connection to the public internet and public AWS services without allowing the Internet to initiate a connection (egress) to your resources.</description></item><item><title>EKS</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/eks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/eks/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki EKS - Elastic Kubernetes Service Amazon EKS provisions and scales the Kubernetes control plane, including the API servers and backend persistence layer, across multiple AWS availability zones for high availability and fault tolerance.</description></item><item><title>Elastic Map Reduce</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/elastic-map-reduce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/elastic-map-reduce/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki EMR - Amazon Elastic Map Reduce Amazon EMR is a manged cluster platform that simplifies running big data frameworks, such as Apache Hadoop and Apache Spark, on AWS to process and analyze vast amounts of data.</description></item><item><title>Elasticache</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/elasticache/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/elasticache/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Elasticache Amazon Elasticache improves the performance of your database through caching query results.</description></item><item><title>Fargate</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/fargate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/fargate/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Fargate AWS Fargate is a general purpose container compute platform. You can run a persistent container that stays up for weeks, and binds to an an IP address to receive HTTP requests and serve web pages, or supply a REST API.</description></item><item><title>FSx for Lustre</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/fsx-for-lustre/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/fsx-for-lustre/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki FSx for Lustre Amazon FSx for Lustre is a high-performance file system for fast processing of workloads.</description></item><item><title>FSx for Windows File Server</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/fsx-for-windows-file-server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/fsx-for-windows-file-server/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki FSx for Windows File Server Amazon FSx for Windows File Server provides fully managed, highly reliable, and scalable file storage that is accessible over the industry-standard Service Message Block (SMB) protocol.</description></item><item><title>GCP Wiki</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/gcp-wiki/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/gcp-wiki/</guid><description> Firestore vs. Firebase Google Cloud Run</description></item><item><title>Gitlab CI/CD</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/gitlab-ci-cd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/gitlab-ci-cd/</guid><description>Using gitlab-runner to test ci locally If on macOS, install gitlab-runner with the below command 1 brew install gitlab-runner To start service, run the below command 1 brew services start gitlab-runner To restart the service, run the below command 1 brew services restart gitlab-runner Official Gitlab Runner Docs: Install GitLab Runner Create a command The following .</description></item><item><title>Global Accelerator</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/global-accelerator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/global-accelerator/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki CloudFront Global Accelerator Similar to CloudFront, in that they both improve performance, but they each do so in different ways, for different reasons.</description></item><item><title>Google Cloud Run</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/google-cloud-run/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/google-cloud-run/</guid><description>nothing yet&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Hot Garlic Honey Glazed Salmon</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/hot-garlic-honey-glazed-salmon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/hot-garlic-honey-glazed-salmon/</guid><description>Ingredients 12 oz. (340 g) Salmon, cut into 2-3 fillet strips Salt Black Pepper 1 pinch of Cayenne Pepper 2 tablespoons of Honey 1 tablespoon warm water 1 tablespoon of Olive Oil 1 tablespoon of Minced Garlic 1 tablespoon of Parsley 1 1/2 teaspoons of Apple Cider Vinegar or Lemon Juice 1/2 lemon, sliced into wedges Instructions Season the surface of the salmon with salt, black pepper and cayenne pepper.</description></item><item><title>IAM</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/iam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/iam/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Identity Access Management IAM Identity Policy Document List of statements that grant or deny permissions to AWS services SID: Optional, but best practice to use Effect Action Resource The identity needs to prove to AWS who it is (authentication) Explicit allows take effect, unless there is also an explicit deny Explicit deny statements overrule everything, nothing can overrule it A deny statement on an IAM policy always takes precedence over an allow statement.</description></item><item><title>IAM Identity Center</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/iam-identity-center/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/iam-identity-center/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki IAM IAM Identity Center (Formerly AWS SSO) Recommended solution for any workforce style identity federation requirements Manage SSO Access - AWS Accounts and External Applications Flexible Identity Source - SSO Integrates with a range of workplace Identity Sources ranging from built-in SSO identities through to self-managed on-premises Active Directory Preferred by AWS vs traditional workforce identity federation (SAML2.</description></item><item><title>If By Rudyard Kipling</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/rudyard-kipling-if/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/rudyard-kipling-if/</guid><description>If you can keep your head when all about you
Are losing theirs and blaming it on you;
If you can trust yourself when all men doubt you,</description></item><item><title>Internet Gateway</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/internet-gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/internet-gateway/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki VPC VPC Router Internet Gateway Region resilient gateway attached to a VPC You do not need a gateway per availability zone 1 VPC = 0 or 1 IGW, 1 IGW = 0 or 1 VPC Runs from within the AWS Public Zone Gateways traffic between the VPC and the Internet or AWS Public Zone (S3, SQS, SNS, etc.</description></item><item><title>IoT Core</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/iot-core/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/iot-core/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki IoT Core AWS IoT Core is a managed cloud service that lets connected devices easily and securely interact with cloud applications and other devices.</description></item><item><title>IP Address</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/ip-address/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/ip-address/</guid><description>When dealing with IP issues, this tool for verifying IP Address in CIDR Range is useful.</description></item><item><title>jq - json parsing cli tool</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/jq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/jq/</guid><description>Modifying a key-value in a JSON file using jq in-place 1 2 contents=&amp;#34;$(jq &amp;#39;.name = &amp;#34;newValue&amp;#34;&amp;#39; package.json)&amp;#34; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; \ echo &amp;#34;${contents}&amp;#34; &amp;gt; package.</description></item><item><title>Kinesis</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/kinesis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/kinesis/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Kinesis Data Streams Amazon Kinesis Data Streams (KDS) is a massively scalable and durable real-time data streaming service.</description></item><item><title>Macie</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/macie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/macie/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki S3 Macie is an ML-powered security service that helps you prevent data loss by automatically discovering, classifying, and protecting sensitive data stored in Amazon S3.</description></item><item><title>Maven Wiki</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/maven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/maven/</guid><description>Maven Resources Apache Maven Docs: Maven CLI Options Reference Apache Maven Docs: Maven CI Friendly Versions Apache Maven Docs: Maven Plugins Difference b/t Common Maven Plugins Maven Commands To view the versions of every dependency used throughout your maven project: 1 mvn dependency:tree Maven Build Lifecycle Quick Summary of Maven Build Lifecycle from the Apache Website Clean clean is it&amp;rsquo;s own build lifecycle phase (which can be thought of as an action or task) in Maven.</description></item><item><title>MQ</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/mq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/mq/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki MQ Amazon MQ is a messaging service that is suitable for anyone using messaging with existing applications and wanting to move their messaging service to the cloud quickly and easily.</description></item><item><title>NACLs and Security Groups</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/nacls-and-security-groups/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/nacls-and-security-groups/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki VPC Network Access Control List (NACL) NACLs are associated with subnets Connections between resources within a subnet are NOT affected by NACLs Each NACL contains 2 sets of rules Inbound Rules - Affect data entering the subnet Outbound Rules - Affect data leaving the subnet These rule sets are only focused on the direction of the traffic, not necessarily whether it&amp;rsquo;s a request or a response.</description></item><item><title>NAT Gateway</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/nat-gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/nat-gateway/</guid><description>Related Notes: AWS Wiki Egress-Only Internet Gateway VPC Gateway Endpoints VPC Interface Endpoints Helpful Links VPC Pricing If you choose to create a NAT gateway in your VPC, you are charged for each “NAT Gateway-hour&amp;quot; that your gateway is provisioned and available.</description></item><item><title>Node</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/node/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/node/</guid><description>Writing an array of JSON to a file from an API in Node Requires axios 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30 31 32 33 34 35 36 37 38 39 40 41 42 43 44 45 46 47 48 49 50 51 52 53 54 55 56 57 58 59 60 61 62 63 64 65 66 67 68 69 70 71 72 73 74 75 76 77 78 79 80 81 82 const axios = require(&amp;#39;axios&amp;#39;); const { writeFile } = require(&amp;#39;fs&amp;#39;); const API_BASE_URL = &amp;#39;https://my-api.</description></item><item><title>Obsidian</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/obsidian/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/obsidian/</guid><description>Plugins Vim Kanban Essentials Basics Open Graph View — Cmd-g Make new note — Cmd-n Create note in new pane — Cmd-shift-n</description></item><item><title>OpenAPI</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/openapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/openapi/</guid><description>Why use OpenAPI? As a tool, OpenAPI allows you to generate client SDKs for your API across dozens of supported languages.</description></item><item><title>OpsWorks</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/opsworks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/opsworks/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki OpsWorks Chef &amp;amp; Puppet help you perform server configuration automatically, or repetitive actions.</description></item><item><title>PrivateLink</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/privatelink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/privatelink/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki VPC Interface Endpoints PrivateLink AWS PrivateLink provides private connectivity between VPCs, AWS services, and your on-premises networks, without exposing your traffic to the public internet.</description></item><item><title>Python</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/python/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/python/</guid><description>Useful Links Pypi: Find, install and publish Python packages Python Virtual Environment Setup Using venv, you can easily work with multiple projects with various dependencies on the same machine at the same time.</description></item><item><title>Recipes</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/recipes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/recipes/</guid><description> Air Fried Frozen Broccoli Bone Broth Rice Blueberry Oatmeal Creamy Tortellini Spinach Chicken Soup Hot Garlic Honey Glazed Salmon Shrimp And Grits Stuffed Bell peppers</description></item><item><title>Redshift</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/redshift/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/redshift/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Redshift Amazon Redshift is a data warehousing solution that can handle data on an exabytes scale.</description></item><item><title>Resource Access Manager</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/resource-access-manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/resource-access-manager/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki RAM - Resource Access Manager AWS RAM is a service that enables you to easily and securely share AWS resources with any AWS account, or within your AWS Organization.</description></item><item><title>Route 53</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/route-53/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/route-53/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Route 53 Health Checks Route 53 Route 53 provides 2 primary services</description></item><item><title>Route 53 Health Checks</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/route-53-health-checks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/route-53-health-checks/</guid><description>Related Notes Route 53 Route 53 Health Checks Health checks are separate from, but are used by records They&amp;rsquo;re configured separately Health checkers located globally Health checkers check every 30s (every 10s costs extra) TCP, HTTP/S, HTTP/S with String Matching Moves between either Healthy or Unhealthy state Endpoint, CloudWatch Alarm, Checks of Checks (Calculated)</description></item><item><title>S3</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki S3 Access Logs S3 Access Points S3 Cors S3 Encryption S3 Events S3 Inventory S3 Lifecycle Configuration S3 Object Lock S3 Object Storage Class S3 Object Versioning and MFA Delete S3 Presigned URLs S3 Replication S3 Select S3 Security S3 Static Website Hosting Simple Storage Service (S3) Amazon S3 now provides increased performance to support at least 3,500 requests per second to add data and 5,500 requests per second to retrieve data, which can save significant processing time for no additional charge.</description></item><item><title>S3 Access Points</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-access-points/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-access-points/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Access Points Simply managing access at scale for applications using shared data sets on S3 buckets.</description></item><item><title>S3 CORS</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-cors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-cors/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 CORS Same-origin requests are always allowed, defined on initial request. Example is an S3 bucket that loads an index.</description></item><item><title>S3 Encryption</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-encryption/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-encryption/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Encryption Buckets aren&amp;rsquo;t encrypted, encryption is defined at the object level 2 methods of encryption that S3 supports, both are encryption at rest.</description></item><item><title>S3 Events</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-events/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Events A feature that allows you to create event notification configurations on a bucket Supports SNS, SQS, Lambda functions, etc.</description></item><item><title>S3 Inventory</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-inventory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-inventory/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Inventory Amazon S3 Inventory is one of the tools Amazon S3 provides to help manage your storage.</description></item><item><title>S3 Lifecycle Configuration</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-lifecycle-configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-lifecycle-configuration/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Object Storage Class S3 Lifecycle Configuration A set of rules, consisting of actions Rules can apply to an entire bucket, or groups of objects Transition Actions move objects to a different Object Storage Class Transitions can only happen in a downward direction Be aware of the 30 day S3 waiting period before you can transition an object Expiration Actions can delete Objects or Object Versions after a certain time period</description></item><item><title>S3 Object Lock</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-object-lock/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-object-lock/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Object Lock Object Lock enables a Write-Once-Read-Many (WORM) - No Delete, No Overwrite</description></item><item><title>S3 Object Storage Class</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-object-storage-class/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-object-storage-class/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Object Storage Classes S3 Standard Objects are replicated across at least 3 AZs in the AWS region Data is available within milliseconds Billed GB/m fee for data stored Billed $ per GB for transfer OUT (IN is free) and a price per 1,000 requests No specific retrieval fee No minimum duration No minimum size S3 Standard-IA (Infrequent Access) Same specs as S3 Standard, but object storage costs are significantly cheaper New cost component, which is a retrieval fee, in the form of a per GB data retrieval fee.</description></item><item><title>S3 Object Versioning and MFA Delete</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-object-versioning-and-mfa-delete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-object-versioning-and-mfa-delete/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Object Versioning Controlled at the bucket level This is disabled by default, but once it is enabled, it CANNOT be disabled, but it can be suspended (which is effectively the same thing) You will continue to be billed for all Object versions, even when Object Versioning is suspended Without Object Versioning being enabled, each object is solely identified by it&amp;rsquo;s key, which is unique inside the bucket If you modify an object, the previous version is deleted Object Versioning allows you to store multiple versions of an object within a bucket When an object with KEY = cat.</description></item><item><title>S3 PreSigned URLs</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-presigned-urls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-presigned-urls/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Presigned URLs Give another person or application access to an object inside of an S3 bucket, using your credentials in a safe and secure way Either you or an automated process can generated a presigned URL, which has specific access permissions encoded within it.</description></item><item><title>S3 Replication</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-replication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-replication/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Replication S3 has replication features which allow objects to be replicated between a SOURCE and DESTINATION bucket in the same or different AWS accounts.</description></item><item><title>S3 Security</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-security/</guid><description>Related Notes s3 Useful Links Bucket Policy Examples S3 Security S3 is private by default.</description></item><item><title>S3 Select</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-select/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-select/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki S3 Athena S3 Select Amazon S3 Select is designed to help analyze and process data within an object in Amazon S3 buckets, faster and cheaper.</description></item><item><title>S3 Static Website Hosting</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-static-website-hosting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-static-website-hosting/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Static Website Hosting Normally, you&amp;rsquo;d use AWS S3 APIs to access S3 However, when S3 Static Website Hosting is enabled, you can access S3 via standard HTTP This allows you to host almost anything When enabling, you must set an Index (default page) and Error (default, when something goes wrong) HTML document When enabled, a Website Endpoint is created.</description></item><item><title>Secrets Manager</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/secrets-manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/secrets-manager/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Secrets Manager</description></item><item><title>Sed</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/jo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/jo/</guid><description>Shell command to create JSON Create JSON with jo</description></item><item><title>Sed</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/sed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/sed/</guid><description>1 sed -i &amp;#39;/^all:/ s/$/ anotherthing/&amp;#39; file</description></item><item><title>Shrimp &amp; Grits</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/shrimp-and-grits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/shrimp-and-grits/</guid><description>Ingredients Shrimp &amp;amp; Bacon Ingredients 4 pieces of bacon, cut in 1/4-inch pieces 1 pound of unfrozen shrimp, peeled and deveined, can be cooked or uncooked 1/2 tsp of Cajun seasoning 1/2 tsp of salt 1/4 tsp of black pepper Pinch of cayenne pepper 1 tbsp of minced garlic 2 tbsp of minced green onion 1 tbsp of minced jalapeno 1 tbsp of chopped parsley Sauce Ingredients 1/4 cup of water 2 tbsp of cream 2 tsp of lemon juice A few drops of Worcestershire sauce Grits Ingredients 1 cup white grits 4 cups water 1 teaspoon salt 2 tablespoons butter 1/2 cup grated white cheddar Cooking Instructions Season Shrimp Take one pound of thawed, thoroughly dried shrimp and throw in bowl with 1/2 tsp Cajun seasoning, 1/2 tsp of salt, 1/4 teaspoon of black pepper, and pinch of cayenne pepper.</description></item><item><title>Simple Notification Service</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/simple-notification-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/simple-notification-service/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Simple Notification Service (SNS) SNS is a fully managed pub/sub messaging service. With Amazon SNS, you can use topics to simultaneously distribute messages to multiple subscribing endpoints such as Amazon SQS queues, AWS Lambda functions, HTTP endpoints, email addresses, and mobile devices (SMS, Push) Messages in an SQS queue will continue to exist even after the EC2 instance has processed it, until you delete that message.</description></item><item><title>Simple Queue Service</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/simple-queue-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/simple-queue-service/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) Amazon SQS is a message queue service used by distributed applications to exchange messages through a polling model.</description></item><item><title>Software Engineering Wiki</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/software-engineering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/software-engineering/</guid><description>Languages &amp;amp; Frameworks Spring Boot Node Python Rust CLI Bash Unix Commands Git curl jed jo jq jEnv jEnv.</description></item><item><title>Spring Boot</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/spring-boot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/spring-boot/</guid><description>Links to each Spring project Spring Data JPA JPQL Docs - Apache Spring Data JPA Official Docs Sorting With Spring Data Baeldung: Sorting Query Results with Spring Data Baeldung: Pagination and Sorting Dynamic sorting with the Spring Data Sort object: A replacement for the ORDER BY clause used in classic SQL Implementation Guides and Tutorials Baeldung: @Query Medium: Pagination example queries in JPQL Baeldung: Transaction Management Wildcard Queries Baeldung: Setting up MetaModel JPA Specifications - Interactive Tutorial JPA Specifications - Interactive Tutorial Hibernate docs - JPA MetaModel Helpful Stack Overflow Posts Difference Between Criteria, Predicate and Specification Criteria API vs QueryDSL vs JPA MetaModel JPA Specifications Spring Boot Actuator Management Endpoints Spring Boot Actuator Endpoints Documentation A useful tutorial for Spring Boot Actuator jEnv For easily managing Java versions across projects Custom Banner in Spring Boot In short, just create a /src/main/resources/banner.</description></item><item><title>Storage Gateway</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/storage-gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/storage-gateway/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Storage Gateway (integrates) AWS Storage Gateway connects an on-premises software appliance with cloud-based storage to provide seamless integration with data security features between your on-premises IT environment and the AWS storage infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Stuffed Bell Peppers</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/stuffed-bell-peppers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/stuffed-bell-peppers/</guid><description>Stuffed bell peppers with ground beef and rice and bake. Sprinkle cheese on top.</description></item><item><title>Systems Manager</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/systems-manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/systems-manager/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Systems Manager Helpful Links Systems Manager Pricing Overview AWS Systems Manager Run Command lets you remotely and securely manage the configuration of your managed instances.</description></item><item><title>Tech Articles</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/tech-articles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/tech-articles/</guid><description> https://scrapeops.io/blog/the-state-of-web-scraping-2022/ https://freenetproject.org/ https://arxiv.org/abs/2201.00223 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cOWjwwKSR78 Raspberry PI E-Ink Dashboard</description></item><item><title>Terraform Wiki</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/terraform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/terraform/</guid><description>Terraform Resources Resource Dependencies Terraform Workspaces When to use Multiple Workspaces Named workspaces allow conveniently switching between multiple instances of a single configuration within its single backend.</description></item><item><title>Tor</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/tor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/tor/</guid><description>The core principle of Tor, Onion routing, was developed in the mid-1990s by United States Naval Research Laboratory employees, mathematician Paul Syverson, and computer scientists Michael G.</description></item><item><title>Transit Gateway</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/transit-gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/transit-gateway/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Direct Connect Transit Gateway The AWS Transit Gateway is a network gateway which can be used to significantly simplify networking between VPC&amp;rsquo;s, VPN, and Direct Connect It can be used to peer VPCs in the same account, different account, same or different region and supports transitive routing between networks Network Transit Hub to connect VPCs to on-premises networks Significantly reduces network complexity, especially as you scale, reduces number of VPN tunnels Single network object - HA and Scalable Highly available inter-VPC router, allows VPCs to talk to each other through the Transit Gateway Support Transitive Routing Share between accounts using AWS RAM Transit Gateways can also be peered with Transit Gateways in other regions or cross account This can be used to create a global network within AWS Creates attachments to other network types VPC Site-to-Site VPN Direct Connect Gateway AWS Transit Gateway is a service that enables customers to connect their VPC Clouds and their on-premises networks to a single gateway.</description></item><item><title>Trusted Advisor</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/trusted-advisor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/trusted-advisor/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Trusted Advisor Account Level product (The service isn&amp;rsquo;t free, but includes a free version with 7 core checks for basic and developer support) AWS Trusted Advisor is an online tool that provides you real-time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices.</description></item><item><title>Unix Commands</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/unix-commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/unix-commands/</guid><description>Cheat Sheets Stanford&amp;rsquo;s Basic Unix Commands Users / Groups To get the current user in a shell or script, run the below command</description></item><item><title>Useful Git Commands</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/git/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/git/</guid><description>Stash Commands Stash tracked files with a stash message 1 git stash save &amp;#34;stash message&amp;#34; Stash tracked and untracked files (-u is shorthand for --include-untracked) with a stash message 1 git stash save -u &amp;#34;stash message&amp;#34; View all stashes 1 git stash list Peek at a stash 1 git stash show -p stash@{0} Apply stash by id (Doesn&amp;rsquo;t delete from stash) 1 git stash apply stash@{0} Unstash a single, specific file from a stash 1 git diff stash@{0}^1 stash@{0} -- &amp;lt;filename&amp;gt; The -p and -u flag step-by-step walks you through each changed/new file in your repo and asks &amp;ldquo;Do you want to stash this?</description></item><item><title>Vim</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/vim/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/vim/</guid><description>Why Vim? Learning to use Vim is worth it for several reasons. First, Vim (or vi) is almost guaranteed to be installed on any remote server you may need to ssh into.</description></item><item><title>VPC Gateway Endpoints</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpc-gateway-endpoints/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpc-gateway-endpoints/</guid><description>Related Notes: AWS Wiki Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) VPC Interface Endpoints VPC Endpoints (Gateway Endpoints) Provides private access to supported AWS services like S3 and DynamoDB (public services) Allows a private-only resource inside of a VPC to access S3 and DynamoDB Allows any resource inside a private-only VPC to access S3 and DynamoDB.</description></item><item><title>VPC Interface Endpoints</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpc-interface-endpoints/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpc-interface-endpoints/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki VPC Gateway Endpoints VPC Endpoints (Interface Endpoints) Similar to VPC Gateway Endpoints, Interface Endpoints allow private access to AWS Public Services.</description></item><item><title>VPC Peering</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpc-peering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpc-peering/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki VPC VPC Peering A service that lets you create a direct, private, encrypted network link between 2 VPCs.</description></item><item><title>VPC Router</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpc-router/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpc-router/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki VPC Internet Gateway VPC Router Every VPC has a VPC Router - Highly available In every subnet .</description></item><item><title>VPN CloudHub</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpn-cloudhub/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpn-cloudhub/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS VPN CloudHub Capable of wiring multiple AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections together on a virtual private gateway.</description></item><item><title>VS Code</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/vs-code/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/vs-code/</guid><description>Search for files: Cmd ⌘+p</description></item><item><title>WorkDocs</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/workdocs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/workdocs/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki WorkDocs Amazon WorkDocs is a fully managed, secure content creation, storage, and collaboration service.</description></item></channel></rss>