<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ec2 on</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/tags/ec2/</link><description>Recent content in ec2 on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wiki.connerv.com/tags/ec2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EBS</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ebs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ebs/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki EBS - Elastic Block Store EBS provides block level storage volumes for use with EC2 instances.</description></item><item><title>EC2</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki EC2 Purchase Options EC2 Placement Groups EC2 - Elastic Compute Cloud Instance Types Instance Types C: Compute Optimized Instances Cost-effective high performance at a low price per compute ratio Note that c1 type instance do not support IPv6 D: Storage Optimized Instances High disk throughput G: Accelerated Computing Instances Graphics-intensive GPU instances H: Storage Optimized Instances HDD-based local storage for high disk throughput I: Storage Optimized Instances High storage instances, low latency, high random I/O performance, high sequential read throughput, and high IOPS M: General Purpose Instances Fixed performance Note that m3 type instance do not support IPv6 P: Accelerated Computing Instances General purpose GPU instances F: Accelerated Computing Instances Reconfigurable FPGA instances R: Memory Optimized Instances Memory-intensive applications T: General Purpose Instances Burstable performance instances X: Memory Optimized Instances Large-scale, enterprise-class, in-memory applications, and high-performance databases EC2 Storage Some EC2 instance types come with a form of directly attached, block-storage known as the instance store.</description></item><item><title>EC2 Placement Groups</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2-placement-groups/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2-placement-groups/</guid><description>Related Notes EC2 EC2 Placement Group Allows you to influence physical placement of EC2 instances within AWS Cluster Placement Groups (Performance) Generally, instances in this placement group will use the same rack, and sometime even the same host.</description></item><item><title>EC2 Purchase Options</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2-purchase-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2-purchase-options/</guid><description>Related Notes EC2 EC2 Purchase Options (Launch Types) On Demand Default purchase option Isolated instances, but multiple customer instances run on the same shared hardware Instances of different sizes run on the same EC2 hosts - consuming a defined allocation of resources Uses per-second billing while an instance is running.</description></item></channel></rss>