<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>aws-compute on</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/tags/aws-compute/</link><description>Recent content in aws-compute on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wiki.connerv.com/tags/aws-compute/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AWS App Runner</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-app-runner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-app-runner/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Useful Links AWS App Runner Pricing AWS App Runner</description></item><item><title>AWS Batch</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-batch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-batch/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Batch AWS Batch is aimed at the specific use case of executing batch jobs that are pulled from a queue.</description></item><item><title>AWS Lambda</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/lambda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/lambda/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Lambda AWS Lambda lets you run code without provisioning or managing servers. You pay only for the compute time you consume.</description></item><item><title>EC2</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ec2/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki EC2 Purchase Options EC2 Placement Groups EC2 - Elastic Compute Cloud Instance Types Instance Types C: Compute Optimized Instances Cost-effective high performance at a low price per compute ratio Note that c1 type instance do not support IPv6 D: Storage Optimized Instances High disk throughput G: Accelerated Computing Instances Graphics-intensive GPU instances H: Storage Optimized Instances HDD-based local storage for high disk throughput I: Storage Optimized Instances High storage instances, low latency, high random I/O performance, high sequential read throughput, and high IOPS M: General Purpose Instances Fixed performance Note that m3 type instance do not support IPv6 P: Accelerated Computing Instances General purpose GPU instances F: Accelerated Computing Instances Reconfigurable FPGA instances R: Memory Optimized Instances Memory-intensive applications T: General Purpose Instances Burstable performance instances X: Memory Optimized Instances Large-scale, enterprise-class, in-memory applications, and high-performance databases EC2 Storage Some EC2 instance types come with a form of directly attached, block-storage known as the instance store.</description></item><item><title>ECS</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ecs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/ecs/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Fargate #ecs- Elastic Container Service Avoid ECS Downtime StackOverflow: Restart ECS service with no downtime To avoid downtime, you should manipulate 2 parameters: minimum healthy percent and maximum percent: For example, if your service has a desired number of four tasks and a maximum percent value of 200%, the scheduler may start four new tasks before stopping the four older tasks (provided that the cluster resources required to do this are available).</description></item><item><title>EKS</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/eks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/eks/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki EKS - Elastic Kubernetes Service Amazon EKS provisions and scales the Kubernetes control plane, including the API servers and backend persistence layer, across multiple AWS availability zones for high availability and fault tolerance.</description></item><item><title>Fargate</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/fargate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/fargate/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Fargate AWS Fargate is a general purpose container compute platform. You can run a persistent container that stays up for weeks, and binds to an an IP address to receive HTTP requests and serve web pages, or supply a REST API.</description></item></channel></rss>