<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>aws-security on</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/tags/aws-security/</link><description>Recent content in aws-security on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wiki.connerv.com/tags/aws-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amazon GuardDuty</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/amazon-guardduty/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/amazon-guardduty/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Amazon GuardDuty Continuous security monitoring service Analyzes supported Data Sources Uses AI/ML, plus threat intelligence feeds Identifies unexpected and unauthorized activity Attempts to learn your normal activity on its own, and spot activity outside of normal patterns Notify or event-driven protection/remediation Supports multiple accounts (MASTER and MEMBER)</description></item><item><title>AWS Config</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-config/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Config Primary function is to record configuration changes over time (configuration items) on resources, and grouping this information into configuration histories</description></item><item><title>AWS Firewall Manager</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-firewall-manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-firewall-manager/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki [[aws-web-application-firewall]] #aws-sysops #aws-security</description></item><item><title>AWS KMS</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-kms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-kms/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki CloudHSM Key Management Service (KMS) Regional and Public Service Every region is isolated when using KMS Create, Store and Manage Cryptographic Keys Allows creation of both symmetric and asymmetric keys Allows you to perform cryptographic operations (encryption, decryption, etc.</description></item><item><title>AWS Service Catalog</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-service-catalog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-service-catalog/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Service Catalog AWS Service Catalog enables a (usually internal user) to directly users or customers to deploy infrastructure with tight control in a self-service way</description></item><item><title>AWS Shield</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-shield/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-shield/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Web Application Firewall AWS Shield Types of Attack Network Volumetric Attacks (L3) - Saturate Capacity These types of attacks overwhelm a system by directing as much raw network data at a target as possible Network Protocol Attacks (L4) - TCP SYN Flood Flood large number of connections, leave connections open, preventing new ones Analogy is people calling a call center, and staying on the phone lines, preventing real customers from talking to call center employees L4 can also have a volumetric component Application Layer Attacks (L7) - e.</description></item><item><title>AWS Web Application Firewall</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-web-application-firewall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-web-application-firewall/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki AWS Firewall Manager Web Application Firewall (WAF) AWS Implementation of Layer 7 firewall (HTTP/HTTPS) The WAF Web ACL can be associated with Global resources like CloudFront, and regional resources, like ALB, API Gateway, etc.</description></item><item><title>AWS X-Ray</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-x-ray/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/aws-x-ray/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki X Ray Distributed tracing application
Tracing Header - first service generates .</description></item><item><title>CloudHSM</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloudhsm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/cloudhsm/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki CloudHSM A cloud based hardware security modules (HSM) that enables you to easily generate and use your own encryption keys on the AWS Cloud.</description></item><item><title>NACLs and Security Groups</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/nacls-and-security-groups/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/nacls-and-security-groups/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki VPC Network Access Control List (NACL) NACLs are associated with subnets Connections between resources within a subnet are NOT affected by NACLs Each NACL contains 2 sets of rules Inbound Rules - Affect data entering the subnet Outbound Rules - Affect data leaving the subnet These rule sets are only focused on the direction of the traffic, not necessarily whether it&amp;rsquo;s a request or a response.</description></item><item><title>S3 PreSigned URLs</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-presigned-urls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-presigned-urls/</guid><description>Related Notes S3 S3 Presigned URLs Give another person or application access to an object inside of an S3 bucket, using your credentials in a safe and secure way Either you or an automated process can generated a presigned URL, which has specific access permissions encoded within it.</description></item><item><title>S3 Security</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/s3/s3-security/</guid><description>Related Notes s3 Useful Links Bucket Policy Examples S3 Security S3 is private by default.</description></item><item><title>Trusted Advisor</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/trusted-advisor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/trusted-advisor/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki Trusted Advisor Account Level product (The service isn&amp;rsquo;t free, but includes a free version with 7 core checks for basic and developer support) AWS Trusted Advisor is an online tool that provides you real-time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices.</description></item><item><title>VPC Peering</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpc-peering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/vpc-peering/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki VPC VPC Peering A service that lets you create a direct, private, encrypted network link between 2 VPCs.</description></item></channel></rss>