<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>efs on</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/tags/efs/</link><description>Recent content in efs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wiki.connerv.com/tags/efs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EFS - Elastic File System</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/efs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/efs/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki EC2 EFS - Elastic File System Moves EC2 to be closer to being stateless Implementation of NFSv4 EFS Filesystems can be mounted in Linux only Uses POSIX permissions, a standard understood by all linux systems Shared between many EC2 Instances Private service, via mount targets inside a VPC Mount targets must be present in each AZ that a VPC uses to provide high availability Mount targets are what the EC2 instances use to connect to the EFS Can be accessed from on-premises via VPN or DX General Purpose and Max I/O performance mode Max I/O is good for highly parallel services Bursting and Provisioned Throughput Modes Storage Classes Standard (default) Infrequent Access (lower cost) Lifecycle Policies can be used with classes Amazon EFS is a fully-managed service that makes it easy to set up and scale file storage in the Amazon Cloud.</description></item><item><title>FSx for Lustre</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/fsx-for-lustre/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/fsx-for-lustre/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki FSx for Lustre Amazon FSx for Lustre is a high-performance file system for fast processing of workloads.</description></item><item><title>FSx for Windows File Server</title><link>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/fsx-for-windows-file-server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wiki.connerv.com/notes/aws/fsx-for-windows-file-server/</guid><description>Related Notes AWS Wiki FSx for Windows File Server Amazon FSx for Windows File Server provides fully managed, highly reliable, and scalable file storage that is accessible over the industry-standard Service Message Block (SMB) protocol.</description></item></channel></rss>